lnkshrnk.net 2019-02-24

# LinkShrink.net - Earn money sharing shrinked links!

## POLICY

**Last Updated:** 19th May 2018

This Privacy Policy describes how Linkshrink collects, uses, and shares information in connection with your use of our Service.

We may collect and receive information about users of our Service ("users," "you," or "your") from various sources, including: (i) information you provide through your user account if you register for the Service and (ii) your use of the Service.

We recommend that you read this Privacy Policy in full to ensure you are fully informed. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or Linkshrink’s data collection, use, and disclosure practices, please do not hesitate to contact us.

This Privacy Policy may be modified from time to time, so please review it frequently. Changes to this Privacy Policy will be posted on our website and we will notify you through a notice.

**Information we collect**

**Account Registration** \- When you register for a publisher account, we will ask for an email address.

**Payment Information** \- We collect payment processing information when you add your financial account information (example Paypal email address or Payoneer email address) and when you request new payments.

**Communications** \- If you contact us directly, we may receive additional information about you such as your name, the contents of the message and/or attachments you may send us, and any other information you may choose to provide.

**Cookies and log data** \- When you use our Service, we may collect certain information automatically from your device. This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, referring/exit pages, operating system, date/timestamp and referring URL. To collect this information, a cookie may be set on your computer or device when you visit our website. Cookies contain a small amount of information that allows our web servers to recognize you. We store information that we collect through cookies and log files to record your preferences. We may also automatically collect information about your use of our website, about the functionality of our Service, frequency of visits, and other information related to your interactions with the Service. 

**How we use information**

We use the information we collect in various ways, including to:

**a.** Administer our Service

**b.** Provide, operate, and maintain our Service

**c.** Improve, personalize, and expand our Service to provide a better experience

**d.** Handle enquiries made by you or about you

**e.** Process your transactions

**f.** Communicate with you through email regarding your account activity or new features

**g.** Find and prevent fraud

**h.** For compliance purposes, including enforcing our Terms of Service

**How we share information**

We may share the information we collect in various ways, including the following:

**a. Service Providers -** We may share information with third-party service providers to process payments.

**b. Advertising -** We work with third-party advertising partners to show you ads that we think may interest you. These advertising partners may set and access their own cookies, pixel tags, and similar technologies on our Service, and they may otherwise collect or have access to information about you which they may collect over time and across different online services.

**c. Information -** If you sign up for our Service through a referral from a friend, we may share information with your referrer to let them know that you used their referral to sign up for our Services.

**d. Analytics -** We use analytics providers such as Google Analytics. Google Analytics uses cookies to collect non-identifying information.

**e. As Required By Law and Similar Disclosures -** We may also share information to (i) enforce this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations; (ii) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security, or technical issues; (iii) respond to your requests; or (iv) protect our rights, property or safety, our users and the public.

**f. With Your Consent -** We may share information with your consent.

**Third Party Services**

You may access other third-party services through the Service, for example by clicking on links to those third-party services from within the Service. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices of these third-party services, and we encourage you to carefully review their privacy policies.

**Data Retention**

We retain personal information we collect from you when we have an ongoing legitimate business. If we have no ongoing legitimate business for the last 1 year, your personal information may be permanently deleted. Publisher account data may also be deleted when requested by you. This may be done by Contacting Us.

**Security**

Linkshrink is committed to protecting your information. We follow generally accepted standards to store and protect the personal data we collect, both during transmission and once received and stored, including utilization of encryption where appropriate.

However, we cannot guarantee that loss, misuse, unauthorized acquisition, or alteration of your data will not occur. Please recognize that you play a vital role in protecting your own personal information. When registering as a Publisher with our Service, it is important to choose a password of sufficient length and complexity, to not reveal this password to any third-parties, and to immediately notify us if you become aware of any unauthorized access to or use of your account.

**Access to Information**

If you are a registered user, you may access, edit and delete certain information associated with your Account by logging into your account. If you terminate your Account, any activity on your Account prior to deletion will be deleted. To protect your privacy and security, we may also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before updating or removing your information.

If you are a registered user, you may request to receive your personal information in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format. This may be done by contacting us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to Contact Us.
